<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Events on CASTogether</title>
    <link>/events/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Events on CASTogether</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/events/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>CAST #1: Busyness</title>
      <link>/events/cast1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/events/cast1/</guid>
      <description>CAST #1: Busyness. How does busyness hinder relationships? Who does being busy well? Why is it so pervasive? What can be done to leverage it for God’s purposes? When must we go against culture and label it an idol? These are some of the conversations and concepts we explored together at this two-hour event for women who want to come alive in Christ. On April 23, 2016, multiple presenters got to speak, sing, and perform on this theme, then engaged with us in immersive settings to discuss and scheme further to carry out God’s work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CAST #2: Restoration</title>
      <link>/events/cast2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/events/cast2/</guid>
      <description>Where are we as people, communities, the Church, and creation broken? What is keeping us from restoration? How can we transcend these obstacles to embrace and advocate wholeness through our Savior? These were some of the conversations and concepts we explored together at this three-hour event on October 15, 2016. Presenters included Renee Ronika, Kit Danley, Amy Jacober, and Alexus Rhone; worship leaders were Rachel O and Suzy Vulaca; and Kristen Miller provided an animation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CAST #3: Waiting</title>
      <link>/events/cast3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/events/cast3/</guid>
      <description>On Good Friday, Jesus died. On Easter Sunday, Jesus rose again. But on Saturday, we waited. Creation waited. Our God waited. Hope seemed dead, darkness the assassin. Call it a cave, call it the dark night of the soul – whatever label you give it, it is a painful time: waiting, hoping, and clinging with nothing but faith that the Light will shine again, that He will redeem our “Saturday”. These were some of the things we discussed at this three-hour event on April 15, 2017, as we explored waiting in three areas: in our personal lives, in the foster care system, and as an oppressed people group waiting on justice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CAST #4: Women</title>
      <link>/events/cast4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/events/cast4/</guid>
      <description>The theme of CAST #4 was Women. We examined it from the personal level of women’s identities, the community level of women in society, and the Church level of women in ministry. A portion of ticket proceeds was donated to Changing Lives Center.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CAST #5: Breaking</title>
      <link>/events/cast5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/events/cast5/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Breaking: deconstruction of faith.
Brokenness: examining our criminal justice system.
Breaking through: redemption and transformation.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>